<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="feature_check_msg">[Çĥéçķîñĝ šûɓšçŕîþţîöñ šţåţûš. Þļéåšé Ŵåîţ... one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_error_msg_title">[Ýöûŕ öŕðéŕ çöûļð ñöţ ɓé þŕöçéššéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_error_msg">"[Îƒ ýöû ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö šûɓšçŕîɓé ţö Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ/Ḿöɓîļé βŕöåðɓåñð Çöññéçţ, çåļļ: 
 Çöñšûḿéŕ: (800) 256-4646, 
 βûšîñéšš: (800) 899-4249. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="tmo_error_msg_title">[ŠéŕVîçé ûþĝŕåðé ŕéQûîŕéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="tmo_error_msg">"[Ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ŕåţé þļåñ ðöéš ñöţ îñçļûðé ţĥé Šḿåŕţþĥöñé Ḿöɓîļé ĤöţŠþöţ šéŕVîçé ŵĥîçĥ éñåɓļéš šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé'š ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš. Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö åðð ţĥé Šḿåŕţþĥöñé Ḿöɓîļé ĤöţŠþöţ šéŕVîçé ţö ýöûŕ ŕåţé þļåñ¿ Ýöû çåñ åļšö åðð îţ öñļîñé åţ ĥţţþš://ḿý.ţ-ḿöɓîļé.çöḿ ûñðéŕ Ḿåñåĝé > Þļåñš åñð ŠéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="app_name">[Éñţîţļéḿéñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="network_connection_title">[Ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ éŕŕöŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="network_connection_error_msg">"[Ýöûŕ þĥöñé çåññöţ çûŕŕéñţļý çöññéçţ ţö »%s«'š šéŕVéŕ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="mobile_hotspot">[Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="spg_dlg_normaltext">[Ţö ûšé Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ, ýöû ŵîļļ ñééð ţö šûɓšçŕîɓé ţö ţĥé Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ šéŕVîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="spg_dlg_linktext">[<a href="https://mobile.vzw.com/hybridClient/mvm/hotspot">Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé åñð šûɓšçŕîɓé ţö Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ ɓý Vîšîţîñĝ Ḿý νéŕîžöñ.</a> one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="browser_error_msg">[Çåññöţ öþéñ ɓŕöŵšéŕ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_positive_button">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_negative_button">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_yes_button">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_no_button">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_upgrade_button">[Ûþĝŕåðé one two]</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_later_button">[Ļåţéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="att_error_msg">[Ţö éñåɓļé, ĝö ţö åţţ.çöḿ/ḿýŵîŕéļéšš öŕ ðîåļ 611 one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="att_error_msg_title">[Åççöûñţ ñöţ šéţ ûþ ƒöŕ ţéţĥéŕîñĝ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="att_error_msg_other">[Ţĥéŕé îš å ţéḿþöŕåŕý ñéţŵöŕķ þŕöɓļéḿ ţĥåţ þŕéVéñţš ţĥé éñåɓļéḿéñţ öƒ ţĥé Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ ƒûñçţîöñ. Þļéåšé ŕéţŕý ļåţéŕ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="att_error_msg_other_title">[Ñéţŵöŕķ Éŕŕöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="sprint_error_msg">[Ûñåɓļé ţö çöññéçţ ţö ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ; Ýöû ḿåý ñöţ ɓé šûɓšçŕîɓéð ţö Ţéţĥéŕîñĝ öŕ Ĥöţšþöţ šéŕVîçé; þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ þĥöñé çöḿþåñý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="sprint_error_msg_lte">[Ýöû åŕé ñöţ šûɓšçŕîɓéð ţö Ţéţĥéŕîñĝ åñð Ĥöţšþöţ šéŕVîçé, Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö šéé šûɓšçŕîþţîöñ öþţîöñš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="sprint_error_msg_3g">[Ûñåɓļé ţö çöññéçţ ţö ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ, ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ Ţéţĥéŕîñĝ öŕ Ĥöţšþöţ. Ýöûŕ þļåñ ḿåý ñöţ ĥåVé ţĥé Ţéţĥéŕîñĝ åñð Ĥöţšþöţ šéŕVîçé. Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö šéé šûɓšçŕîþţîöñ öþţîöñš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]</string>
    <string name="sprint_error_msg_title">[Ţéţĥéŕîñĝ öŕ Ĥöţšþöţ Éŕŕöŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="sprint_notification_msg">[Ţöûçĥ ţö šéé ḿöŕé ðéţåîļš one two three]</string>
    <string name="att">[ÅŢ&amp;T</string>
    <string name="verizon">[νéŕîžöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="tmo">[Ţ-Ḿöɓîļé one two]</string>
    <string name="sprint">[Šþŕîñţ one two]</string>
</resources>
