<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="suw_next_button_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_back_button_label">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_more_button_label">[Ḿöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="app_label">[Çåŕŕîéŕ Šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="entitlement_check_progress">[Çĥéçķîñĝ šûɓšçŕîþţîöñ šţåţûš. Þļéåšé ŵåîţ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="att_service_upgrade_msg">[Ţö éñåɓļé, ĝö ţö åţţ.çöḿ/ḿýŵîŕéļéšš öŕ ðîåļ 611 one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="att_network_error">[Ñéţŵöŕķ ûñåVåîļåɓļé. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="sprint_entitlement_error">[ŠéŕVîçé ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ šéŕVîçé þŕöVîðéŕ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="sprint_network_error">[Ñéţŵöŕķ ûñåVåîļåɓļé. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_service_upgrade_msg">[Ţö ûšé Ḿöɓîļé Ĥöţšþöţ, þļéåšé çåļļ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé ţö šûɓšçŕîɓé. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_network_error">[Ñéţŵöŕķ ûñåVåîļåɓļé. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_wfc_activation_error">[Ûñåɓļé ţö åçţîVåţé ŴîFî çåļļîñĝ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_update_error">[Ûñåɓļé ţö ûþðåţé ţĥé çûŕŕéñţ éḿéŕĝéñçý åððŕéšš åţ ţĥîš ţîḿé. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="generic_error">[Åûţĥéñţîçåţîöñ ƒåîļéð. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_setup_app_label">[νéŕîžöñ Åççöûñţ ÅçţîVåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_title">[Þĥöñé åçţîVåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_progress">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ ŵĥîļé ŵé þŕéþåŕé ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_exiting">[Éхîţîñĝ åçţîVåţîöñ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_title">[νéŕîƒý ýöûŕ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_ssn">"[Ţö ĝéţ šţåŕţéð, éñţéŕ ţĥé ļåšţ 4 ðîĝîţš öƒ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ öŵñéŕ'š Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ: one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_pwd">"[Ţö ĝéţ šţåŕţéð, éñţéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ'š ɓîļļîñĝ þåššŵöŕð: one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_button">[νéŕîƒý one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_later_button">[Ļåţéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_switch_ssn">[Ûšé Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ îñšţéåð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_switch_pwd">[Ûšé ɓîļļîñĝ þåššŵöŕð îñšţéåð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_progress_title">[νéŕîƒýîñĝ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_title">[Ŕéåðý ţö åçţîVåţé¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_new">[Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé å ƒéŵ ḿîñûţéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_upgrade">"[βéƒöŕé ýöû åçţîVåţé ţĥîš þĥöñé, ɓåçķ ûþ ýöûŕ çöñţåçţš åñð ţûŕñ öƒƒ ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé.

Öñçé ýöû šţåŕţ åçţîVåţîöñ, ŵé'ļļ ţŕåñšƒéŕ ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ ţö ţĥîš þĥöñé åñð ðéåçţîVåţé ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_button">[ÅçţîVåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_new_title">[Ĝéţţîñĝ þĥöñé ñûḿɓéŕ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_upgrade_title">[Ţŕåñšƒéŕŕîñĝ þĥöñé ñûḿɓéŕ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_upgrade">[Ţö ţŕåñšƒéŕ ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ ţö ýöûŕ ñéŵ þĥöñé, ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé ñééðš ţö ɓé ţûŕñéð öƒƒ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_success_title">[Þĥöñé åçţîVåţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_success">[Ýöûŕ νéŕîžöñ þĥöñé îš ñöŵ åçţîVé. Ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ îš %1$s one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_limit_title">[Ðåţå ûšåĝé ļîḿîţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_limit">[Ýöûŕ ðåţå ûšåĝé îš çûŕŕéñţļý ļîḿîţéð ðûé ţö ţîḿé öƒ ðåý öŕ å ðåţå ļîḿîţ. Ýöû ŵîļļ ñééð ţö ûšé Ŵî-Fî ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_restricted_title">[Ðåţå ûšåĝé ļîḿîţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_restricted">[Ðûé ţö ţîḿé öƒ ðåý öŕ å ðåţå ļîḿîţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_redirected_title">[Ĝéţ νéŕîžöñ šéŕVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_redirected">"[Ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåVé å νéŕîžöñ Ŵîŕéļéšš þļåñ öŕ ýöû'Vé ûšéð åļļ öƒ ýöûŕ þļåñ åļļöŵåñçé, þļéåšé çöñţåçţ νéŕîžöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_notification_title">[Ŕéåðý ţö åçţîVåţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_notification">[Ţåþ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_cold_notification">[Çöñţåçţ νéŕîžöñ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_title">"[Çåñ'ţ åçţîVåţé one two]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_network">[Ḿåķé šûŕé ýöû ĥåVé å ĝööð šîĝñåļ (ḿûļţîþļé ɓåŕš) åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. Îƒ ţĥîš þŕöɓļéḿ þéŕšîšţš, þļéåšé çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204 ƒöŕ åššîšţåñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_lookup">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_ssn">[Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ ðöéš ñöţ ḿåţçĥ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_pwd">[βîļļîñĝ þåššŵöŕð ðöéš ñöţ ḿåţçĥ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_not_retryable">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_release">[Ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé, çåļļ (800) 922-0204 ƒŕöḿ åñöţĥéŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_restricted_title">[Ĥöŵ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_restricted">[Ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé, ƒöļļöŵ ţĥé îñšţŕûçţîöñš îñçļûðéð ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ñéŵ þĥöñé öŕ çöñţåçţ ţĥé νéŕîžöñ Ŵîŕéļéšš åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ åţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_lost_stolen">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Þļéåšé çåļļ (877) 807-4646 ƒŕöḿ åñöţĥéŕ þĥöñé ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ 4Ĝ ĻŢÉ šéŕVîçé åñð ţĥéñ ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_retry">[Ŕéţŕý one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_skip">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="emergency_address_app_label">[Éḿéŕĝéñçý Åððŕéšš Ḿåñåĝéḿéñţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="progress_text">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ… one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_title">[ÅçţîVåţé Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_text">"[Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ ļéţš ýöû ţö ḿåķé çåļļš ûšîñĝ Ŵî-Fî ŵĥéñ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ îš ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé.

Ţö šéţ ûþ Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ, ýöû ŵîļļ ñééð ţö éñţéŕ å ÛŠ åððŕéšš. Ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð ɓý éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš îñ ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ îƒ ýöû ḿåķé åñ éḿéŕĝéñçý (É911) çåļļ öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî ƒŕöḿ ţĥîš þĥöñé ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé ÛŠ.

Ŵé ŕéçöḿḿéñð ýöû çĥåñĝé ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵĥéñ ýöû ḿåķé çåļļš ûšîñĝ å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ šö ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ îš åççûŕåţé. Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñý ţîḿé ɓý ĝöîñĝ ţö Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ šéţţîñĝš ḿéñû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_link">[Ţéŕḿš åñð Çöñðîţîöñš one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_title">[Éḿéŕĝéñçý Ļöçåţîöñ Îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_description">[<b>ÎḾÞÖŔŢÅÑŢ - ÉḾÉŔĜÉÑÇÝ 911 ÅÐÐŔÉŠŠ ŔÉqÛÎŔÉÐ</b>"
Ţö ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ, éñţéŕ ţĥé Û.Š. åððŕéšš ŵĥéŕé ýöû ŵåñţ éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš šéñţ îƒ ýöû çåļļ 911. Ýöû çåñ ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš åñð çĥåñĝé ţĥîš åððŕéšš åţ åñý ţîḿé. Îţ îš Véŕý îḿþöŕţåñţ ţö ûþðåţé ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵĥéñéVéŕ ýöû çĥåñĝé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_warning">[<b>ŴÅŔÑÎÑĜŠ - ÉḾÉŔĜÉÑÇÝ 911 ÇÅĻĻ ĻÎḾÎŢÅŢÎÖÑŠ</b>"
Ŵĥéñ çåļļîñĝ 911, åļŵåýš ţéļļ ţĥé öþéŕåţöŕ ŵĥéŕé ýöû åŕé. Ýöûŕ 911 çåļļ ŵîļļ ĝö öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî öñļý îƒ ţĥé çéļļûļåŕ ñéţŵöŕķ îš ûñåVåîļåɓļé. 911 çåļļ ḿåðé öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî ḿåý ɓé ðéļåýéð öŕ ûñšûççéššƒûļ; ƒöŕ éхåḿþļé, îƒ ţĥé 911 šýšţéḿ ðöéšñ'ţ ŕéçöĝñîžé ţĥé åððŕéšš, éļéçţŕîçåļ þöŵéŕ îš öûţ, öŕ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî çöññéçţîöñ îšñ'ţ ŵöŕķîñĝ. Éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš ŵîļļ ɓé šéñţ ţö ţĥé åððŕéšš ýöûŕ þŕöVîðéð åɓöVé, šö þļéåšé ûþðåţé îţ åš ýöû çĥåñĝé ļöçåţîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="house_number">[Åððŕéšš Ñûḿɓéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="street">[Šţŕééţ one two]</string>
    <string name="apt_suite_number">[Åþţ, Šûîţé, éţç. one two three]</string>
    <string name="city">[Çîţý one]</string>
    <string name="state">[Šţåţé one]</string>
    <string name="zip_code">[Žîþ çöðé one two]</string>
    <string name="save">[ŠåVé one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_confirm_text">"[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ţĥé åððŕéšš ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ɓéçåûšé ţĥé šţŕééţ åððŕéšš çöûļð ñöţ ɓé ƒöûñð, öŕ ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ çöðé ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ.

Îƒ ýöûŕ çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ åŕé ñöţ çöŕŕéçţ ţåþ %1$s, öţĥéŕŵîšé ţåþ %2$s. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_confirm_text_part1">[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ţĥé åððŕéšš ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ɓéçåûšé ţĥé šţŕééţ åððŕéšš çöûļð ñöţ ɓé ƒöûñð, öŕ ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ çöðé ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_confirm_text_part2">[Îƒ ýöûŕ çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ åŕé ñöţ çöŕŕéçţ ţåþ %1$s, öţĥéŕŵîšé ţåþ %2$s. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="save_anyway">[ŠåVé Åñýŵåý one two]</string>
    <string name="edit_address">[Éðîţ Åððŕéšš one two]</string>
    <string name="ok">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_select_text">[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ţĥé åððŕéšš ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_alternate_text">[Ðîð ýöû ḿéåñ: one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_confirm_head">[Ţĥé åððŕéšš éñţéŕéð çöûļð ñöţ ɓé Våļîðåţéð ɓý Éḿéŕĝéñçý ŠéŕVîçé ÞŕöVîðéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_confirm_text">[Åŕé ýöû šûŕé ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ûšé ţĥîš åððŕéšš îñ çåšé öƒ åñ éḿéŕĝéñçý¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_failure_text">"[Ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, öŕ žîþ çöðé ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ.

Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ţĥé åððŕéšš åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_failure_text_part1">[Ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, öŕ žîþ çöðé ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_failure_text_part2">[Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ţĥé åððŕéšš åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five]</string>
</resources>
