<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="suw_next_button_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_back_button_label">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_more_button_label">[Ḿöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="app_label">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé šéţûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="provisioning_error_title">[Ööþš¡ one]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_profile">[Šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="company_controls_workspace">[Ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ çöñţŕöļš ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé åñð ķééþš îţ šéçûŕé. Ýöû çöñţŕöļ éVéŕýţĥîñĝ éļšé öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="company_controls_device">[Ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ ŵîļļ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ðéVîçé åñð ķééþ îţ šéçûŕé. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="the_following_is_your_mdm">[Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ ñééð ţö åççéšš ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="the_following_is_your_mdm_for_device">[Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ ḿåñåĝé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé: one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="next">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="setting_up_workspace">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_profile">"[Ýöûŕ åðḿîñ ĥåš ţĥé åɓîļîţý ţö ḿöñîţöŕ åñð ḿåñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕḿîššîöñš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîVîţý, åš ŵéļļ åš ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý, åñð çöñţåçţ šéåŕçĥ ĥîšţöŕý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]"</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_device">"[Ýöûŕ åðḿîñ ĥåš ţĥé åɓîļîţý ţö ḿöñîţöŕ åñð ḿåñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕḿîššîöñš, ţĥéƒţ-þŕöţéçţîöñ ƒéåţûŕéš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš ðéVîçé, îñçļûðîñĝ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîVîţý åñð ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="theft_protection_disabled_warning">[Ţö ûšé ţĥéƒţ-þŕöţéçţîöñ ƒéåţûŕéš, ýöû ḿûšţ ĥåVé å þåššŵöŕð-þŕöţéçţéð šçŕééñ ļöçķ ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="contact_your_admin_for_more_info">"[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ åðḿîñ ƒöŕ ḿöŕé îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîVåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="learn_more_link">[Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="ok_setup">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="user_consent_msg">[Î çöñšéñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="default_managed_profile_name">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two]</string>
    <string name="default_first_meat_user_name">[Þŕîḿåŕý ûšéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="delete_profile_title">[ŔéḿöVé ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="opening_paragraph_delete_profile_unknown_company">[Å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé åļŕéåðý éхîšţš åñð îš ḿåñåĝéð ɓý: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="opening_paragraph_delete_profile_known_company">[Ţĥîš ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš ḿåñåĝéð ƒöŕ »%s« ûšîñĝ: one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="read_more_delete_profile">[βéƒöŕé þŕöçééðîñĝ, <a href="#read_this_link">ŕéåð ţĥîš</a>. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="sure_you_want_to_delete_profile">[Îƒ ýöû çöñţîñûé, åļļ åþþš åñð ðåţå îñ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ ɓé ðéļéţéð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="delete_profile">[Ðéļéţé one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_delete_profile">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_profile_owner_setup">"[Ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé, ýöû'ļļ ñééð ţö éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé šöḿé ţîḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_device_owner_setup">"[Ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé, ýöû'ļļ ñééð ţö éñçŕýþţ îţ. Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé šöḿé ţîḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_launch_settings">[Éñçŕýþţ one two]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_title">[Éñçŕýþţîöñ çöḿþļéţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_text">[Ţåþ ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="managed_provisioning_error_text">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ öŕ ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="managed_provisioning_not_supported">"[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ðöéšñ'ţ šûþþöŕţ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļéš one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="user_cannot_have_work_profile">[Ţĥîš ûšéŕ çåññöţ ĥåVé å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_exists">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļéš çåñ ñöţ ɓé šéţûþ öñ å ḿåñåĝéð ðéVîçé one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="maximum_user_limit_reached">"[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé çåñ'ţ ɓé çŕéåţéð ɓéçåûšé ýöû'Vé ŕéåçĥéð ţĥé ḿåхîḿûḿ ñûḿɓéŕ öƒ ûšéŕš öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. ŔéḿöVé åţ ļéåšţ öñé ûšéŕ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="managed_provisioning_not_supported_by_launcher">"[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îšñ'ţ šûþþöŕţéð ɓý ţĥîš ļåûñçĥéŕ åþþ. Ýöû'ļļ ñééð ţö šŵîţçĥ ţö å ļåûñçĥéŕ ţĥåţ'š çöḿþåţîɓļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="cancel_provisioning">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="pick_launcher">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="user_setup_incomplete">[Ûšéŕ Šéţûþ Îñçöḿþļéţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="default_owned_device_username">[Ûšéŕ öƒ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_device">[Šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_data_process">[Þŕöçéššîñĝ šéţûþ ðåţå… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_connect_to_wifi">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö Ŵî-Fî… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_download">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_install">[Îñšţåļļîñĝ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_set_owner">[Šéţţîñĝ ţĥé ðéVîçé öŵñéŕ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="preprovisioning_error_encryption_not_supported">[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ðöéš ñöţ šûþþöŕţ éñçŕýþţîöñ. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_cancel_message">"[Šţöþ šéţţîñĝ ûþ åñð éŕåšé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ðåţå¿ one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_cancel_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_ok">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_reset">[Ŕéšéţ one]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_general">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_already_provisioned">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé îš åļŕéåðý šéţ ûþ. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_wifi">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî one two three]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_frp">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé îš ļöçķéð ɓý ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ þŕöţéçţîöñ. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="frp_clear_progress_title">[Éŕåšîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="frp_clear_progress_text">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ... one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_hash_mismatch">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ ðûé ţö å çĥéçķšûḿ éŕŕöŕ. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_download_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_package_invalid">"[Çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ. Îţ'š ḿîššîñĝ çöḿþöñéñţš öŕ çöŕŕûþţéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_installation_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ îñšţåļļ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_message">[Šţöþ šéţţîñĝ ûþ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_cancel">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_ok">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancelling">[Çåñçéļîñĝ… one two]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_later_title">[Šţöþ þŕöƒîļé šéţûþ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_later_message">[Ýöû çåñ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ļåţéŕ ƒŕöḿ ţĥé ðéVîçé ḿåñåĝéḿéñţ åþþ ûšéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_stop">[Šţöþ one]</string>
    <string name="provisioning">[ÞŕöVîšîöñîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="copying_certs">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ÇÅ çéŕţîƒîçåţéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_start_setup">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Šţåŕţ šéţûþ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_start_setup">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Šţåŕţ šéţûþ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_label">[Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé ɓûţţöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="mdm_icon_label">[%1$s îçöñ one]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_title">[Éñð šéţûþ åñð ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ¿ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_msg">[Éñðîñĝ ţĥîš šéţûþ ŵîļļ ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð ţåķé ýöû ɓåçķ ţö ţĥé ƒîŕšţ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_ok">[Ŕéšéţ ðéVîçé one two]</string>
</resources>
